trueads.com 2008-01-06

# TrueAds - Internet Advertising

Site: TrueAds  
URL: http://www.TrueAds.com 

TrueAds has created this privacy statement in order demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
This site uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.

This site uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the Web.

This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.

**Personal Information**  
TrueAds collects your name and email address, and other pertinent information. 

This information is used to facilitate buying and selling of links/advertisements on the Internet.

We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes beyond those stated here.

Visit [http://www.TrueAds.com](http://www.trueads.com/) and click **"Edit Account"** to update your personal information.

**Cookies**  
This site uses cookies for session management. See the Session Management section for more information about how cookies are used.

**Session Management**  
This site uses form elements and/or cookies on each page to maintain a continuous user session.

Form elements and/or cookies may contain a unique ID that identifies your browser session.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location.

All credit card information is encrypted with 40-bit SSL encryption before it is transmitted across the network.

TrueAds complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.

**Contact Information**  
TrueAds complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact info@TrueAds.com
